

# DANE KILPATRICK FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

### SKILLS

Javascript React Git/Github Node.is HTML Express CSS MongoDB jQuery SQL/NoSQL Bootstrap Python Materialize Django **AngularJS** 

# PROFILE

I am an adaptable and creative web developer. I pursue collaborative projects that have a meaningful and impactful outcome on everyday life. I utilize my experience in the Air Force and technology sales to help resolve current problems in the most efficient way possible. I have a passion for the aesthetic side of web development that impacts the overall experience of the user.

# SOCIAL





✓ Dkilpatrick1990@Gmail.com



Linkedin.com/in/danekilpatrick



803-931-6992

Adopt A Woof | CRUD app built in Python with DjangoDB

Happy Hour | A happy hour locator app using Express, NodeJS and MongoDB

Tic Tac Toe | Used Javascript to create functional Tic Tac Toe game

GeoQuakes | Earthquake tracking app using Jquery and Google Maps API

#### EXPERIENCE

#### Mainstreet Hub | Inside Sales Representative

2016 - 2017

2016 - 2016

2013 - 2015

- Managed full sales cycles from cold-calling to demonstrations, through closing.
- Consistently met and exceeded daily call goals above 120 cold-calls per day.
- Scheduled and executed online product demos with prospective clients.

#### InoApps | Business Development Manager

- Developed business plan & strategies, evaluated strategic opportunities, optimize systems for monitoring & reporting business performance.
- Prospected potential corporations who could utilize Oracles Cloud Services followed by communication introduction part of the sale on a CO level.
- Developed training and onboarding process for new hires.

#### United States Air Force | Surveillance Technician

- Apart of a global team using the BC3T radar systems to detect and identify in friendly and combat air spaces and performed 864 Command and Control hours.
- Provided Combat Identifications for over 8000 missions in Afghanistan, Iraq and the Arabian Gulf.
- Prepared the duty and training schedule for 77 coalition personnel which included 14 crew positions/56 shifts daily and assisted in 35 High-Value Airborne Asset ISIL/Taliban Target Strikes.

# EDUCATION | TRAINING

**Web Development Immersive** 2017 - 2017

**General Assembly** 

Air and Space Operations Technology 2013 - 2015 Keesler AFB, Luke AFB, Spangdahlem AB

2009 - 2011 **General Studies** 

Holmes Community College